[
    {
        "id": "84",
        "question": "In a group of 10 people, 8 like Physics, 10 like Maths, and 8 like both. How many people like Physics only?",
        "options": [
            9,
            6,
            0,
            7
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "id": "34",
        "question": "In a group of 10 people, 6 like Physics, 8 like Maths, and 4 like both. How many people like Physics only?",
        "options": [
            2,
            2,
            8,
            3
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "id": "71",
        "question": "In a group of 10 people, 6 like Physics, 6 like Maths, and 2 like both. How many people like Physics only?",
        "options": [
            4,
            7,
            3,
            4
        ],
        "correct": 4
    },
    {
        "id": "84",
        "question": "In a group of 10 people, 4 like Physics, 8 like Maths, and 2 like both. How many people like Physics only?",
        "options": [
            6,
            2,
            8,
            6
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "id": "39",
        "question": "The initial value was 7, and the new value is 1. What is the percentage change?",
        "options": [
            -86.0,
            -89.0,
            -80.0,
            -85.0
        ],
        "correct": -86.0
    },
    {
        "id": "33",
        "question": "The initial value was 5, and the new value is 4. What is the percentage change?",
        "options": [
            -17.0,
            -20.0,
            -25.0,
            -13.0
        ],
        "correct": -20.0
    },
    {
        "id": "67",
        "question": "The initial value was 2, and the new value is 9. What is the percentage change?",
        "options": [
            350.0,
            347.0,
            358.0,
            353.0
        ],
        "correct": 350.0
    },
    {
        "id": "86",
        "question": "An athlete's chances of qualifying for the Highland Games changed from 1% to 6%. What is the absolute percentage change and the relative percentage change?",
        "options": [
            "Absolute: 7%, Relative: 521.0%",
            "Absolute: 8%, Relative: 517.0%",
            "Absolute: 5%, Relative: 500.0%",
            "Absolute: 4%, Relative: 493.0%"
        ],
        "correct": "Absolute: 5%, Relative: 500.0%"
    },
    {
        "id": "44",
        "question": "An athlete's chances of qualifying for the Highland Games changed from 9% to 6%. What is the absolute percentage change and the relative percentage change?",
        "options": [
            "Absolute: 5%, Relative: 49.0%",
            "Absolute: 5%, Relative: 56.0%",
            "Absolute: 1%, Relative: 24.0%",
            "Absolute: 3%, Relative: 33.0%"
        ],
        "correct": "Absolute: 3%, Relative: 33.0%"
    },
    {
        "id": "84",
        "question": "The initial price was 6, and the new price is 5. What is the percentage change?",
        "options": [
            -9.0,
            -22.0,
            -13.0,
            -17.0
        ],
        "correct": -17.0
    }
]